{
	"questions":
	[
		{
			"category": "Condition",
			"question": "Symptoms: restless, irritable, weak, confused, dizzy, afraid. Moist, clammy, cool, pale skin. Quick, weak pulse. Shallow, rapid, irregular breathing. Nauseated, vomiting. Extremely thirsty. \n Treatment: Restore breathing and circulation, control bleeding, relieve pain, treat wounds. Ensure airway stays open. If no nervous system injuries, have them lie down. Raise feet about 12 inches to increase blood flow to vital organs. Keep victim warm.",
			"answer": "Shock"
		},
		{
			"category": "Rescue Assist",
			"question": "Place one victim's arm around your neck and hold that hand. Place other arm around victim's waist to support their weight",
			"answer": "Walking assist"
		},
		{
			"category": "Rescue Assist",
			"question": "Drag a person by both ankles over a smooth surface if they cannot otherwise be moved and you do not suspect a nervous injury",
			"answer": "Ankle drag"
		},
		{
			"category": "Rescue Assist",
			"question": "For rough surfaces or if a person has a nervous injury. Grab clothing behind the shoulder and pull",
			"answer": "Shoulder drag"
		},
		{
			"category": "Rescue Assist",
			"question": "Roll person onto a blanket or tarp and pull them using the covering",
			"answer": "Blanket drag"
		},
		{
			"category": "Rescue Assist",
			"question": "Carry a person who does not weigh much and you do not suspect has a nervous injury by placing one arm under their knees and one around their upper back",
			"answer": "One-person lift"
		},
		{
			"category": "Rescue Assist",
			"question": "If you do not suspect a nervous injury and need to travel a longer distance, carry a person over your shoulder",
			"answer": "Firefighter carry"
		},
		{
			"category": "Rescue Assist",
			"question": "If you do not suspect a nervous injury, carry a person on your back and have them cross their arms in front of you. Suitable for long distances",
			"answer": "Pack-strap carry"
		},
		{
			"category": "Rescue Assist",
			"question": "If victim is conscious, not in shock, and does not have a suspected nervous injury, have the victim place an arm around each of the two rescuers' necks and hold their far hands. Rescuers place their free hands around the victim's waist, and rescuers support victim's weight as they walk",
			"answer": "Helping the person walk"
		},
		{
			"category": "Rescue Assist",
			"question": "If victim is conscious and can hold onto rescuers, have two rescuers form a square with their hands by grabbing onto their own and each other's wrists. Have the victim sit on the resulting square.",
			"answer": "Four-handed seat"
		}
	]
  }
  